Guide to the George White Papers, 1932-1970 M1111
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1. Papers and Correspondence
  - Rosaro Pisciotta, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Notes from recording made at Hotel New Yorker, October 24, 1950; 7 typed pp. (carbons)
    - Transcript of a wire recording made at Hotel New Yorker, December 17, 1950; 3 typed pp. (carbons)
    - Investigation report by Leo Palier re: stakeout of Hotel New Yorker, October 27, 1950; 1 p. typed(carbons)
    - Statement by Robert L. Kimball re: drug purchase, October 24, 1950; 4pp. signed
    - TLS to H. J. Anslinger from James C, Ryan re: Robert L. Kimball, October 5, 1950; 3pp. (carbons)
    - Newsclippings re: motion to withdraw guilty plea by Rosaro Pisciotta, March 1952
  - William Burkett, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - ALS to GW from William Burkett on Treasury Dept. stationary, re: congratulations, March 3, 1950; 2pp.
    - TLS to GW from William Burkett re: Senate Investigation, December 7, 1950; 2pp.
    - Confidential memo to H. J. Anslinger from GW re:William Burkett, December 27, 1950; 6p. (carbons)
    - ALS to GW from William Burkett re: discharge accusation, January 11, 1951, 2pp. encl/ discharge papers of William Burkett from U.S. Coast Guard; January 20, 1945,
      Scope and Contents note
      1p. (photocopy)
    - ALS to GW from William Burkett re: speech, January 20, 1951, 2pp. encl/ text of Speech - Taxes and Political Corruption; January 24, 1951,
      12pp. (carbons)
    - TLS to GW from William Burkett re: Kefauver committee, February 20, 1951; 2pp.
    - TLS to GW from William Burkett re: Olney, May 3, 1951; 1p.
    - TLS to GW from William Burkett re: visit, May 14, 1951; 1p.
    - TLS to GW from William Burkett re: Steffen, October 2, 1951; 1p.
    - TLS to GW from William Burkett re: Kefauver committee, November 30, 1951; 2pp.
    - TLS to GW from William Burkett re: Intelligence Unit, January 29, 1952; 2pp.
    - TLS to William Burkett from GW re: recommendation, February 1, 1952; 2pp.
    - TLS to GW from William Burkett re: crime commission, May 13, 1952; 2pp.
    - TLS to GW from William Burkett re: Congressional run, March 10, 1952; 2pp.
    - TLS to GW from William Burkett re: Newbold Morris, April 8, 1952; 2pp.
    - TLS to GW from William Burkett re: Nixon, January 30, 1952; 1p.
    - TLS to GW from William Burkett re:visit August 15, 1952, 1p.
    - TLS to GW from William Burkett re: visit, November 15, 1952; 1p.
    - ALS to GW from Julie Burkett, December 7, 1952; 2pp.
    - TLS to GW from William Burkett re: censure, December 10, 1952; 1p.
    - TLS to William Burkett from GW re: Olney, February 13, 1953; 3pp.(photocopies)
    - TLS to GW from William Burkett re: tax probe, May 21, 1953; 2pp.
    - TLS to William Burkett from GW re: psycho accusations, May 26, 1953; 2pp. (photocopies)
    - TLS to GW from William Burkett re: tax scandal, July 6, 1953; 2pp.
    - TLS to GW from William Burkett re: appointment to Director, 1p. w/ attached progress report, State of California Department of Employment / by William Burkett, November 15, 1953 - February 15, 1954; 4pp. (carbons)
    - TLS to GW from William Burkett re: departmental accomplishments, July 21, 1955 1p. w/ Statement from the Congressional Report June 10, 1955 re: re-instatement of William Burkett as Senior Special Agent
    - Newsclippings re: William Burkett, c. 1953; (photocopies)
  - Dr. John E. Jackson (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - TLS to T. W. McGeever from GW re: Dr. John E. Jackson, October 11, 1940; 11pp. (carbons)
    - Investigation Report of Bureau of Narcotics re: Homocide of Dr. John E. Jackson, March 6, 1959; 3 pp. (carbons)
    - Investigation Report of Bureau of Narcotics re: Information relative to the homocide of Dr. John E. Jackson, April 17, 1959; 4 pp. (carbons)
  - Rudolph Halley, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - TLS to GW from Rudolph Halley on Fulton, Walter, & Halley stationary re: congratulations, July 29, 1951; 1p.
    - TLS to GW from Rudolph Halley on Fulton, Walter, & Halley stationary re: visit, August 10, 1951; 1p.
    - TLS to GW from Rudolph Halley on Fulton, Walter, & Halley stationary re: vacation, August 18, 1951; 1p.
    - TLS to GW from Rudolph Halley on City of New York stationary re: opium seizure, October 31, 1952; 1p.
    - TLS to GW from Rudolph Halley on campaign stationary re: election, November 1, 1953; 1p.
    - Memo to Rudolph Halley from George re: Brown - Moretti, 1p. (carbons)
    - Memo to Max from GW re:Rudolph Halley, November 26, 1952; 1p. (carbons)1p.
    - Memo to Rudolph Halley from GW re: implications of SCC hearings, November 30, 1952; 1p. (carbons)
    - TLS to GW from Rudolph Halley re: visit, September 2, 1955; 1p.
    - 3 news clippings on election results-
    - Halley campaign button
    - Halley Headquarters pass signed "George White"
    - 5 Elect Halley pamphlets
    - Elect Halley Bumper sticker
  - Herlands, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Confidential report from GW re: interview w/ Mr. Herlands, NY State Commisioner of Investigation, April 4, 1954; 5p. (carbons)
    - TLS to GW from Charlie (Charles Siragusa, district supervisor) re: Herlands report, January 25, 1955
  - Houston Narcotics Investigation, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Holograph report of drug seizure by J. T. Conley & E. H. Bennett, August 11, 1953; (photocopy)
    - TLS to Will Sears from H. Chapman Rose re: unscrupulous conduct of GW, June 21, 1954; 1p. (photocopy)
    - TLS to GW from M. re: drug investigation, July 4, 1953; 1p. (photocopy)
    - Memo Report from Vance Newman re: Investigation of William McCafferty, June 15, 1954; 1p.
    - Narcotic Case Report from Vance Newman re: Investigation of Foy Melton, June 20, 1954; 1p.
    - Transcript of interview w/ Larry Fultz, June, 1954; 11pp. (carbons)
    - Memo report re: list of witnesses beofre Grand Jury, June 21, 1954; (photocopy)
    - Memo Report from Vance Newman re: Investigation at Police headquarters, June 22, 1954; 1p.
    - Memo Report from Vance Newman re: Investigation of Morrison, July 7, 1954; 1p.
    - Memo Report from Vance Newman re: Investigation Dr. Jack Cooper, July 8, 1954; 1p.
    - TLS to GW from M. re: drug investigation, August 6, 1954; 1p. (photocopy)
    - TLS to GW from M. re: drug investigation, August 10, 1954; 1p. (photocopy)
    - TLS to GW from M. re: drug investigation, August 21, 1954; 1p. (photocopy)
    - TLS to GW from M. re: drug investigation, August 23, 1954; 1p. (photocopy)
    - TLS to GW from M. re: drug investigation, August 24, 1954; 1p. (photocopy)
    - TLS to GW from M. re: drug investigation, August 25, 1954; 1p. (photocopy)
    - Memo to GW from H. J. Anslinger re: allegations of impropriety, November 30, 1954; 1p.
    - TLS to H. J. Anslinger from GW re: denial of allegations, December 6, 1954; 2pp. (carbons)
    - TLS to GW from Neal Matthews re: lawyer, January 9, 1956
    - w/ Memo Report from Vance Newman re: Investigation at Police headquarters, June 21, 1954, June 22, 1954; 1p.
    - TLS to GW from H. G. Robinson on Office of the Attorney General stationary re: Houston police, March 15, 1956; 2pp.
    - Newsclippings
    - 2 8x10 photos of GW in car on stakeout w/ detectives McCafferty, Minor, & McCormick, June 9, 1954
  - W C Pool, 1954/ 55 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - TLS to Chief Heard from W. C. Pool re: allegations of misconduct, September 17, 1954
    - Office Memo to GW from Fred J. Douglas re: charges against W. C. Pool, January 17, 1955; 2pp.
    - Telegram, to GW from W. C. Pool re: civil service request, February 7, 1955
    - ALS to GW from W. C. Pool re: McCleary, February 26, 1955; 2p. (photocopy)
    - ALS to GW from W. C. Pool from Las Vegas re: Katleman, Saturday Eve.; 2pp.
    - ALS to GW from W. C. Pool re: Greenspun, May 30, 1955; 2pp.
    - ALS to GW from W. C. Pool re: dismissal, June 2, 1955; 1p. w/ newsclipping
    - TLS to Al Ferguson, Commissioner of Police from GW re: recommendation for W. C. Pool, July 25, 1955; 4pp. (photocopy)
    - ALS to GW from W. C. Pool re: Morrison case, August 9, 1955; note
    - TLS to GW from Fred (Douglas)on Treasury Dept stationary re: recommendation for POOL, August 9, 1955; 1p.
    - ALS to GW from W. C. Pool re: Greenspun, August 12, 1955; note
    - ALS to GW from W. C. Pool re: appointment to sergeant, undated; 1p. (photocopy)
    - TLS to Fred J. Douglas from Malcolm Wilkey re: W. C. Pool, August 24, 1955; 2pp. (photocopy)
    - TLS to GW from W. C. Pool on Police Department stationary re: assignment as Chief of Police, September 2, 1955; 1p. (photocopy)
    - TLS to GW from W. C. Pool, Chief of Police on Police Department stationary re: Sidney Smith, September 17, 1955; 1p.
    - TLS to GW from J. T. Conley on Gateway Hotel, El Paso TX stationary re: W. C. Pool, September 17, 1955; 3pp. (photocopy)
    - TLS to GW from W. C. Pool, re: charges filed against him, October 20, 1956; 1p.
    - TLS to GW from W. R. McNinch, Las Vegas Police Department re: charges against W. C. Pool, November 21, 1956; 2pp.
    - ALS to GW from W. C. Pool re: Internment in Terminal Island facility, December 24, 1958; 1p. w/ transcription
    - TLS to GW from W. C. Pool re: appointment as chief of police, October 19, 1961; 1p.
    - Newsclippings (photocopies) of press stories regarding charges against W. C. Pool
  - Sidney Smith, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Case Report by Vance Newman re: Sidney Smith, July 3, 1954; 4pp. (photocopy)
    - TLS to Fred J. Douglas from Vance Newman re: drugs obtained by Carl Lawder for Sidney Smith, July 5, 1954; 1p. (photocopy)
    - TLS to Malcolm Wilkey from GW re: Sidney Smith, August 9, 1954; 1p. (photocopy)
    - Deposition of Sidney Smith re: re-trial motion, May 1st, 1956; 4pp. (carbons)
    - Petitioners exhibit "A" - Sworn Statement by Marguerite Frederick repudiating her testimony against Sidney Smith, July 6, 1955; 3pp. (carbons)
    - Petitioners exhibit "B" - Sworn Statement by Charles Aaron re: drugs obtained by Carl Lawder for Sidney Smith, June 17, 1955; 1p. (carbons)
    - Affidavit of GW stating allegations made by Sidney Smith in deposition of May 1st 1956 are false, May 9, 1956
    - TLS to GW from Carlos G. Watson re: Sidney Smith motion for re-trial
  - The Luciano Story, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Press release from author of The Luciano Story Joachim Joesten repudiating facts printed in his book
    - Analysis of the book by GW, 3 pp.
    - Analysis of the book by Charles Siragusa, 3 pp.
    - TLS from GW to Estes Kefauver re: The Luciano Story, January 25, 1955; 1p. (carbons)
    - TLS from GW to Carl Victor Little re: The Luciano Story, January 6, 1955; 1p.(carbons)
    - TLS from GW to Charlie Siragusa re: The Luciano Story, January 25, 1955; 1p.(carbons)
    - TLS from GW to John re: The Luciano Story, January 25, 1955; 1p. (carbons)
    - TLS from GW to John re: The Luciano Story, January 25, 1955; 1p. (carbons) w/ reply
    - TLS from J. Spaulding Arrington to GW re: The Luciano Story, January 21, 1955; 1p.(carbons)
    - TLS from Malcolm R. Wilkey to GW re: The Luciano Story, January 21, 1955; 1p. (carbons)
    - TLS from J. W. Ehrlich to GW re: The Luciano Story, January 18, 1955; 1p. (carbons)
  - Foy Melton, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Subpoenea to testify GW, January 26, 1955
    - Telegram to GW from Malcolm re: Melton Acquittal
    - Newsclipppings
  - Enzensperger, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - TLS to Bob Gifford, District Attorney re: Enzensperger case, February 24, 1956; 4pp. w/ carbon copy
    - TLS to GW from H. J. Anslinger re: Enzensperger case, March 20, 1956, 1p w/ copy of letter to George M. Dickerson from H. J. Anslinger re: Enzensperger case
    - TLS to GW from H. J. Anslinger re: contact w/ district attorney, March 21, 1956; 1p. (carbon)
    - TLS to J. G. Melville from Charles Shreve, re: nomination of GW for award, May 28, 1956; 3pp.
    - Pamphlet - The American Tradition in 1957 w/ "the case of the 9 pound suitcase"
    - Newsclippings re: Enzensperger case, c. March 1956
  - Braumoeller, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - TLS to GW from Ira C. Feldman re: Braumoeller narcotic sales, September 12, 1957
    - Newsclippings re: arrest of state narcotics officer Braumoeller on charges of selling confiscated drugs to criminals.
  - Billnitzer Death, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - TLS to GW from Fred re: gun used in Billnitzer death, October 29, 1958; 2pp.
    - TLS to GW from Neil Matthews re: gun used in Billnitzer death, October 29, 1958; 2pp.
    - TL, to Malcolm Wlikey from unknown re: gun used in Billnitzer death, December 22, 1958; 2pp.
    - TLS to Smith & Wesson from Neil Matthews re: gun used in Billnitzer death, November 6, 1956; 1p. (Photocopy)
    - TLS to Neil Matthews from Smith & Wesson re: gun used in Billnitzer death, November 9, 1956; 1p. (Photocopy)
    - TLS to Galef & Son from Neil Matthews re: gun used in Billnitzer death, November 12, 1956; 1p. (Photocopy)
    - TLS to Neil Matthews from Galef & Son re: gun used in Billnitzer death, November 14, 1956; 1p. (Photocopy)
    - TLS to W. T. Grant Company from Neil Matthews re: gun used in Billnitzer death, November 15, 1956; 1p. (Photocopy)
    - TLS to W. T. Grant Company from Neil Matthews re: gun used in Billnitzer death, November 16, 1956; 1p. (Photocopy)
    - TLS to GW from Neil Matthews re: gun used in Billnitzer death, January 8, 1959; 2pp.
    - TLS to GW from Neil Matthews re: Grand Jury trial, October 20, 1959; 1p. (Photocopy)
  - Albert Jackson, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Criminal record of Albert Jackson
    - Newsclippings re: shooting and arrest of Albert Jackson-
- Series 2. Correspondence and Newsclippings
  - Publishing correspondence, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Letters re: various articles proposed and published on GW's exploits
    - Letters and memos re: proposed series on White for Saturday Evening Post by Dean Jennings and bureau policy
  - Retirement, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 14 8x10 glossy photos of reception for retirement dinner of GW
    - TLS to GW from William J. Raggio re: retirement dinner, September 21, 1965; 1pp.
    - Announcement on Treasury Department stationary of retirement and dinner, April 14, 1965
    - Newsclippings re: retirement of GW
  - Private Investigation, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and application forms forms to register as operative in California
  - Famous Writers School, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Writing exercises by Arthur J. Guiliani
    - Meet the Instructor
  - A Diet of Danger, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Carbon copies of GW's partial autobiography
    - Outline for autobiography, 14pp.
    - North of San Francisco, where the lonely -, 4pp.
    - Preamble This is not only the story of my life..., 3pp.
    - Chapter I "a reader of a book..., 6pp.
    - Chapter I The Hard Way, 26pp.
    - An autobiography could be called "a diet of danger"..., 14pp.
    - Chapter V Murder Incorporated "Fish" Adelman, 49pp.
    - Chapter VI (Patterson) One of the less pleasant..., 32pp.
    - Chapter XVIII Came my chance - The trapping of the Mexican Colonel "He was a wonderfully croaked character..., 25pp
    - Also includes holograph notes, correspondence w/ agents & publishers, contracts, etc.
  - Departmental Papers, Reports, announcements, memos, rosters, and correspondence re: Narcotics Bureau (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Departmental Corrrespondence (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - John Arrington, 1938 - 1953 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Personal correspondence to GW from J. Spaulding Arrington, San Francisco journalist
  - Correspondence: Pre- 1950 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous letters to/ from GW
  - Correspondence: 1950 - 1960 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous letters to/ from GW
  - Correspondence: post 1960 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous letters to/ from GW
  - Kaplan - White Correspondence, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - "An address made before the Law Forum of Stanford University Law School on October 28, 1970 by Geo H. White, 24pp. - 2 copies
    - Letters to/from John Kaplan, Stanford Law School re: Legalization of Marijuana
    - Book Reviews - Marijuana - The New Prohibition by John Kaplan by Malachai Harney
    - Letters to /from Malachai Harney re: Marijuana
    - "Clinical Notes on the use of Marijuana" by D. Harvey Powelson, 7pp. - 4 copies
    - Letters to /from D. Harvey Powelson re: Marijuana
    - Newsclippings re: John Kaplan / Marijuana use
  - Correspondence post -retirement, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Personal letters to/from GW circa 1970
  - Popskull Corresponce (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Letters to/ from Red Popskull, college of saloon surgeons
- Series 3. Newsclipping Files
  Photocopies of newpaper articles selected by GW
  - Biographical newclippings (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Pat Somerset, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Misc Newsclippings, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Kefaufer crime hearings, 1950/51 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings of Kefaufer tax investigations Clippings re: death of Shelby Sommerset
  - Misc Newsclippings, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Misc Newsclippings, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Samish Tax Hearings, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Steffen Tax case, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Lucchese, Gaetano, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Lane Probe, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Ecuador, March 23, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Lucky Luciano, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Rinaldo "Red" Ferrarri, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Narcotics (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Mafia (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Misc Newsclippings (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Misc Columns (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - George White affidavit re. Jean Pierre Lafitte (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous handwritten notes (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Series 4. Magazines and Publications
  - Paper - "Control and Elimination of Opium and Narcotics", 23pp. w/ 2 maps Burma (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous publications (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Pamphlet "How can we stop making drug addicts of our children?" - panel w/ GW
    - Marihuana: Its Identification July 1938 U.S. Treasury Department: Bureau of Narcotics
    - Congressional Record July 19, 1953 "The Iniquitous Narcotics Traffic"
    - People Magazine 1952 (partial)w/ "White vs. Crooks"
    - Instruction Manual 1952 - Miles Walkie-Recordall "on the spot" Battery Recorder
    - New Republic November 19, 1951 w/ "The Tax Thieves of 1951"
    - "How can we stop making Drug addicts of our children"
  - Various articles/publications (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - True Magazine, December 1959 w/ True Crime series case #1 "When the Rookie took the Tong" by James Phelan (Flat-box 6)
  - True Magazine, December 1959 w/ True Crime series case #3 "The Cops who Sold (Flat-box 6)
  - True Magazine January 1960 as w/ True Crime series case #2 "The Calculating Colonel and the Turkish Trap" by James Phelan (Flat-box 6)
  - "Dope" by James Phelan (Flat-box 6)
  - Argosy Magazine w/ "Undercover Trap", November (Flat-box 6)
  - Argosy Magazine November 1955 w/ article "Dope-buster" by Michael Stern -, 2 copies (Flat-box 6)
  - Marin Magazine Saturday April 3, 1971 w/ "The Perilous Game of the Narcotic Agent" by Pat Angle -, 5 copies (Flat-box 6)
  - Man's Magazine September 1961 w/ I Peddled Dope for the Houston's Cops by Charles "Red" Aaron Inmate #159982 (Flat-box 6)
  - Real Magazine July 1953 w/ The Mystery of the Hopped-up Mouse by Martin Abramson (Flat-box 6)
  - Official Detective Stories October 1956 w/ "When they Stole for Junk" by Ray Jackson (Flat-box 6)
  - True Police Cases September 1956 w/ "The Strange Case of the Framed Schoolteacher" by Jay Hubert (Flat-box 6)
  - Inside Detective June 1956 w/ "Is This Justice?" by Hugh Coburn (Flat-box 6)
  - Official Detective Stories August 1956 w/ "ten Years for Eleven Pounds" by Weston Wahl (Flat-box 6)
  - The American Tradition in 1957 w/ The case of the 9 pound Suitcase -, 2 copies (Flat-box 6)
  - Time Magazine March 12, 1951(Cover Estes Kefauver) w/ "Crime: It Pays to Organize" (Flat-box 6)
  - Chicago Free Press September 28, 1970 w/ "Some Marines Smoke Pot - So What Else is New" by Janes Tuohy (Flat-box 6)
- Series 5. Notebooks and Diaries (Box 7)
  - GW address book
  - Daily appointment books, 51/2 x 81/2"spiral bound, 1957, '60, '61, '62, '65, '70, '71
  - Daily appointment books, 3 x 6" black, 1934, '35, '36, '37, '38, '39, '40, '41, '42, '43, '44, '45, '46, '47, '48, '49, '55, '54, '51, '52, '56, '58, '59
  - Envelope containing passports and identity cards for GW
  - Envelope containing various business cards and ephemera
- Series 6. Personal photographs (Flat-box 8)
  - Envelope of personal photos of GW, his wife and friends
  - Envelope w/ Christmas cards
  - 8 x 10 photo of personnel of Bureau of Narcotics agency dated, February 2, 1961
  - Signed 8 x 10 photo of Henry L. Giordano (Head of Narcotics Bureau, 1962)awarding safe driving award to unknown person signed "to the personnel of district #14"
  - Series of 8 x 10 photos of drug seizure
  - 8 x 10 photo of Henry L. Giordano awarding safe driving award to unknown trio
  - 5x7 photo in sleeve of GW, and party at Sammy's Bowery Follies
  - 5 x 7 photo of GW w/ others at dinner in restaurant
  - 8x10 photo of plant labeled Lophophora Williams 7 - 53
  - 8x10 photo of GW seated at desk
  - Signed 8x10 glossy photo of Lana Wong
  - Signed 8x10 glossy photo of Janis Page
  - Signed 7 x 9 glossy photo of Charles Siragusa
  - Signed 7 x 9 glossy photo of Newbold Morris
  - Signed 8x10 glossy photo of Garland Williams
  - Signed 8 x 10 photo of John H. Haney (Rear Admiral, USNR)
  - Signed 8x10 glossy
  - 8x10 photo of opium addict w/ pipe
  - Signed 5x7 photo of Bob Patterson
  - Signed 5x7 photo of Kaye
  - 8x10 photo Quito, March 53 - GW posing w/ John Nakervis, Mayor Felix Guerno, and
  - Rafael Toledo after drug bust
  - 8 x 10 photo - GW w/ associates
  - 8 x 10 photo of the Press & Union League Club w/ speaker GW
  - Folder Artwork and caricatures - political cartoons and sketches of GW
  - Certificate of Appreciation - County of Marin
  - Certificate of Appreciation - Stanford Law Forum- Col. George Hunter White
  - Certificate of Appreciation - Stanford Law Forum - Col. George A. White
  - Certificate for Exceptional Service - U. S. Treasury Dept., October 30, 1949
  - Honorable Service Citation - Office of Strategic Services -, October 1, 1945
  - Certificate Ordine Militare dei Cavaliere del Soccorso -, September 24, 1948
  - Coat of Arms - City of Calcutta
  - Framed Identity card for GW from Mexico-, May 27, 1949
  - Framed signed letter from Estes Kefauver
  - Framed certificate Sea Ip Church, Calcutta India
- Series 7. Scrapbooks
  - Scrapbook of George White (Flat-box 9)
  - Binder - "Investigations participated in by federal narcotic agents in District #2 (New York State and Northern New Jersey) during period October 1946 to March 1947 inclusive"letters, articles, photos, agency documents bound in chronological order by George White (Flat-box 9)
  - Large scrapbook (Flat-box 10)